I would say that in the next five years, if you aren't deep diving in being something
more, then a re-excript kitty.
If you aren't understanding your terminal, understanding them, becoming the best you
can be, becoming the person that can do stuff that's really deep and difficult, I would
say that.
Yeah, you're probably going to be obsolete pretty quickly.
We'd say that.
Yeah, you're probably going to be obsolete pretty.
Okay.
Next 10 years?
Yeah.
Well, but if you're the one that can figure stuff out and you go deep, you're going
to be the one that's not obsolete.
You should figure out how to become an amazing programmer.
You should at some point tweet.